Guide to the Time Inc. People Publishing and Business Records 1973-2003 MS 3009-RG 27
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Publisher Richard Durrell Files, 1973-1983; 56.25 Linear feet in 57 record cartons
  - Subseries I.B. Subject Files, 1973-1983; 55.25 Linear feet in 56 record cartons
    - Conventions: National Association of Food Chains: Los Angeles: October 18-20, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 20)
    - Covers: Tests, Etc., 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 21)
    - Delivery: Traffic Study, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 22)
    - Dinah Show Taping: May 6, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 23-24)
    - Filler Space, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 25)
    - Five Year Plan, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 26)
    - Golf: Arcata Outing: Aspetuck, New York: October 7, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 27)
    - Golf: Blind Brook: September 9, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 28)
    - Golf: Sour Mash Tournament: May 13-14, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 29)
    - Golf: Time Inc. Golf Outing: Shoreacres: Chicago: June 8, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 30)
    - International, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 31)
    - International: Japan, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 32)
    - Legal, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 33)
    - Legal: Logo, Etc., 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 34)
    - Letters: Miscellaneous, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 35)
    - Lists: Mailings, Etc., 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 36)
    - Luncheons: Agency-Advertisers, Etc., 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 37)
    - Mailing: Power Shift: May, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 38)
    - Meetings: Advertising Sales Staff: New York and Greenwich: August 4-5, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 39)
    - Memoranda: Barnet, Bruce, 1976 (Offsite-box 2951, Folder 40)
    - Memoranda: Edit, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 1)
    - Memoranda: Elliman, Don, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 2)
    - Memoranda: Fisler, Bob, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 3)
    - Memoranda: Hall, Bill, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 4)
    - Memoranda: Keylor, Art, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 5)
    - Memoranda: Meier, Joe, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 6)
    - Memoranda: Ochs, Mal, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 7)
    - Memoranda: Posthorn, Stan, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 8)
    - Memoranda: Posthorn and Vecchio: Posters, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 9)
    - Memoranda: Stolley, Dick, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 10)
    - Memoranda: Thomas, Dick, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 11)
    - Memoranda: Valk, Garry, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 12)
    - Memoranda: Vecchio, Donna: Covers, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 13)
    - Memoranda: Walsh, Bill, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 14)
    - National Enquirer, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 15)
    - National Star, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 16)
    - People to People, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 17)
    - People Shopper, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 18)
    - Permissions, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 19)
    - Personnel, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 20)
    - Photographers, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 21)
    - Presentations, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 22)
    - Pricing: Regulations, Tests, Etc., 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 23)
    - Promotion: Air, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 24)
    - Promotion: Air: Horror Movies, Etc., 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 25)
    - Promotion: Air: Quadra, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 26)
    - Promotion: Consumer: Circulation, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 27)
    - Promotion: Print, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 28)
    - Publicity: Air, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 29)
    - Publishers Estimate, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 30)
    - Publisher's Letter, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 31)
    - Rates, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 32)
    - Requests for Appearances: Advertising Clubs, Schools, Etc., 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 33)
    - Research, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 34)
    - Select Marketing: Correspondence, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 35)
    - Staff Memoranda: Durrell, Dick, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 36)
    - Staff Memoranda: Miscellaneous, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 37)
    - Staff Memoranda: Posthorn, Stan, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 38)
    - Staff Memoranda: Thomas, Dick, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 39)
    - Stanford Court: San Francisco, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 40)
    - Starch, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 41)
    - Stores: A & P, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 42)
    - Stores: Giant Food Stores, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 43)
    - Stores: Safeway, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 44)
    - Stores: Stop and Shop (Louis Banks), 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 45)
    - Stores: Weingarten, Lufkin, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 46)
    - Stores: Winn-Dixie, Etc. (Heiskell), 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 47)
    - Store Checks, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 48)
    - Store Check By Ad Salesmen, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 49)
    - Strike, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 50)
    - Syndication: Print, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 51)
    - Test Markets, 1976 (Offsite-box 2952, Folder 52)
    - Time Distribution Services: A.R.A., 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 1)
    - Time Distribution Services: Correspondence, 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 2)
    - Time Distribution Services: Meetings, 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 3)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores, 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 4)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Kroger, 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 5)
    - Time Distribution Services: Wholesalers, 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 6)
    - Time Distribution Services: Wholesalers Incentive Program, 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 7)
    - Time-Life Films, 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 8)
    - Time-Life Films: NBC Television Show, 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 9)
    - Time-Life Films: Television Shows, 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 10)
    - Trades: Swaps, 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 11)
    - Trades: Swaps: Air, 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 12)
    - Two Year Plan, 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 13)
    - Universal Product Code (UPC), 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 14)
    - Us, 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 15)
    - Weekly Reports to Art Keylor, 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 16)
    - Women, 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 17)
    - Year-End Issue, 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 18)
    - Branch Offices: Los Angeles: Party, 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 19)
    - Branch Offices: Washington, D.C., 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 20)
    - Branch Offices: West Coast, 1976 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 21-22)
    - Act Media, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 1)
    - Ad Council, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 2)
    - Ad Pages: Limiting, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 3)
    - Advertising Age, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 2)
    - Ad Director's Letter, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 3)
    - Alberse, Jim, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 4)
    - Airline Research, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 5)
    - Applications, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 6)
    - Audience Analysis, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 7)
    - Awards, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 8)
    - Bonuses, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 9)
    - Budget, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 5)
    - Budgets: Ad Sales, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 10)
    - Budgets: Circulation, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 11)
    - Budgets: Edit, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 12)
    - Budgets: Promotion, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 13)
    - Clips: Articles, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 14)
    - Clips: General, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 15)
    - Clips: People, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 16)
    - Clips: Supermarkets, Chains, Etc., 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 17)
    - Cole, Monger, And Waterhouse Inc., 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 18)
    - College Market, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 6)
    - Company Plane, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 19)
    - Complimentary Lists, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 20)
    - Conventions, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 21)
    - Conventions: Food Marketing Institute: Boca Raton: January 19-22, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 22)
    - Conventions: Cosmetic, Toiletry and Fragrance Association: Boca Raton: February 27-March 3, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 23)
    - Conventions: Energy Conference: Williamsburg: April 5-8, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 24)
    - Conventions: Western Association of Food Chains, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 25)
    - Conventions: Proprietary: May 16-17, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 26)
    - Conventions: Food Marketing Institute: May 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 27)
    - Conventions: Joint ANA/MPA/4A's Sesssion: New York: June 22, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 28)
    - Conventions: Creative Conference: July 10-13, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 29)
    - Conventions: Ad Age Media Workshop: Chicago: August 18, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 30)
    - Conventions: Food Marketing Institute: Atlanta: October 21-25, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 31)
    - Conventions: National Association of Convenience Stores: Toronto: September 18-22, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 32)
    - Conventions: Western American Association of Advertising Agencies: October 16-19, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 33)
    - Conventions: Housing Conference, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 34)
    - Copy Acceptance, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 35)
    - Covers, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 7)
    - Cover Tests, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 8)
    - Donohue Show, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 36)
    - Filler Space, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 37)
    - Five Year Plan, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 38)
    - Free Space Requests, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 39)
    - Golf, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 40)
    - Golf: Stoneacres Golf Club: Chicago: June 7, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 41)
    - Golf: NAGA: September 17, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 42)
    - Golf: La Quinta: December 8-9, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 43)
    - Helgeson, John, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 44)
    - Ideas for People, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 45)
    - International, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 9)
    - Issue Review, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 10)
    - Legal, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 11)
    - Legal: Logo, 3090 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 12)
    - Letters: Miscellaneous, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 46)
    - Letters: Replies to "The Gamesman", 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 47)
    - Letters: Requests for Story Coverage, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 13)
    - Letters: Too Much Advertising, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 14)
    - Luncheons/Dinners, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 48)
    - Memoranda: Clare Crawford Book, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 15)
    - Memoranda: Crutcher, Larry, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 49)
    - Memoranda: Edit, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 50)
    - Memoranda: Elliman, Don, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 51)
    - Memoranda: Keylor, Art, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 52)
    - Memoranda: Jones, Charlotte, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 53)
    - Memoranda: Miscellaneous, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 54)
    - Memoranda: Posthorn, Stan, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 55)
    - Memoranda: Raley, Deane, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 56)
    - Memoranda: Shepley, Jim, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 57)
    - Memoranda: Valk, Garry, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 58)
    - Merchandising, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 16)
    - National Enquirer, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 17)
    - National Star, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 18)
    - People-to-People, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 19)
    - Paper Quality, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 59)
    - Party: Halloween: October 27, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 60)
    - Permissions, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 20)
    - Personnel, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 61)
    - Photo Exhibition, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 21)
    - Photographers, Etc., 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 22)
    - Posters, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 23)
    - Poster Campaign, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 24)
    - Presentations: People Film, 1977 (Offsite-box 3061, Folder 62)
    - Presentations: Miller Brewing: May 11, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 1)
    - Pricing: Regulations, Tests, Etc., 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 2)
    - Promotion: Air, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 3)
    - Promotion: Television: Flighted vs. Control, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 4)
    - Rates: Corporate Discount, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 25)
    - Rate Increase, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 26)
    - Rebates: Advertising Complaints, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 27)
    - Research, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 28)
    - Sales Meeting: Bermuda: May 3-6, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 5)
    - Sales Staff: Durrell, Dick, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 6)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Lund, Chuck, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 7)
    - Sales Staff Memoranda: Thomas, Dick, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 29)
    - Speeches, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 8)
    - Speech Requests, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 9)
    - Store Checks, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 10)
    - Television: David Susskind Show, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 30)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 11)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: A & P, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 12)
    - Time Distribution Services: Stores: Stop And Shop (Lous Banks), 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 13)
    - Time Distribution Services: Wholesalers, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 14)
    - Time-Life Films, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 31)
    - Time-Life Films: NBC, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 32)
    - Television and Television Shows, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 15)
    - Television: Special Edition, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 16)
    - Temple-Eastex, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 17)
    - Third Anniversary Party: March 3, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 18)
    - Universal Product Code, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 19)
    - Us, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 20)
    - Weekly Report: Keylor, Art, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 21)
    - Women, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 34)
    - Year End Issue, 1977 (Offsite-box 3090, Folder 35)
    - Young & Rubicam Promotion, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 22)
    - Branch Office: Detroit, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 23)
    - Branch Office: Los Angeles, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 24)
    - Branch Office: Texas, 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 25)
    - Branch Office: Washington, D.C., 1977 (Offsite-box 3062, Folder 26)
    - Ad Council, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 23)
    - Airlines: Subscriptions, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 24)
    - Alberse, Jim, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 25)
    - Analysis: Breseman, Herb, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 26)
    - Annual Report, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 27)
    - Apparel Category, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 28)
    - Applications, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 29)
    - Automotive Category, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 30)
    - Bloomingdale Poster Program, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 31)
    - Awards, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 32)
    - Budget, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 33)
    - Budgets: Ad Sales, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 34)
    - Budgets: Circulation, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 35)
    - Budgets: Cost and Profit, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 36)
    - Budgets: Edit, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 37)
    - Budgets: H-Low Volume Requirement, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 38)
    - Budgets: Production, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 39)
    - Budgets: Promotion, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 40)
    - Canada, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 41)
    - Cigarette Category, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 42)
    - Circulation, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 43)
    - Circulation: All Magazines, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 44)
    - Clips: Articles, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 45)
    - Clips: People, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 46)
    - Clips: Supermarket, Chains, Etc., 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 47)
    - College Market, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 48)
    - Company Plane, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 49)
    - Complaints: Advertising, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 50)
    - Comp Lists, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 51)
    - Conference: Board of Directors: Lyford Cay: November 15-16, 1978 (Offsite-box 2953, Folder 52-53)
    - Conference: Housing Conference: December 10-14, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 1)
    - Conventions, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 2)
    - Conventions: Dinners, Luncheons, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 3)
    - Conventions: Middle East Tour, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 4)
    - Conventions: Suggested Material, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 5)
    - Conventions: Food Marketing Institute Midwinter: Boca Raton: January 8-11, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 6)
    - Conventions: Detroit Auto Show: January 13, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 7)
    - Conventions: Housewares Show: Super Bowl Screening: January 15, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 8)
    - Conventions: Hilton Head: February 10-12, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 9)
    - Conventions: Cosmetics, Toiletries, and Fragrance Association: Boca Raton: February 26-March 2, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 10)
    - Conventions: American Advertising Federation: March 18, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 11)
    - Conventions: Western Association of Food Chains: San Antonio: March 23-26, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 13)
    - Conventions: Corporate Manufacturing and Distribution: Sawgrass: April 9-11, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 12)
    - Conventions: National Association of Chain Drug Stores: April 9-12, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 15)
    - Conventions: Food Marketing Institute: Dallas: April 30-May 1, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 14)
    - Conventions: Board of Directors Reception: Chicago: May 17, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 16)
    - Conventions: American Advertising Federation Award: Dinner-Dance: June 2, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 17)
    - Conventions: Time Sales Meeting: Kiawah: June 4-8, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 18)
    - Conventions: Magazine Publishing Week: June 12, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 19)
    - Conventions: Creative Conference: Cambridge: June 18-21, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 20)
    - Conventions: Taxation Conference: Washington, D.C.: September 13-14, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 21)
    - Conventions: National Association of Chain Stores: Los Angeles: September 24-28, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 22)
    - Conventions: Magazine Publishers Association and the American Society of Magazine Editors: Pheonix: October 15-18, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 23)
    - Conventions: Food Marketing Institute: New Orleans: October 21-25, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 24)
    - Conventions: Creative Conference: 1979, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 25)
    - Copy Acceptance, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 26)
    - Copy Processing (Decentralization), 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 27)
    - Corporate Manufacturing and Distribution, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 28)
    - Cosmopolitan, 1978 (Offsite-box 2954, Folder 29)
    - Couponing, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 1)
    - Cover Tests, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 2)
    - Covers, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 3)
    - Covers for Merchandising, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 4)
    - Covers from Other Magazines, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 5)
    - Covers: Research, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 6)
    - CPDA News, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 7)
    - Cross Fertilization, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 8)
    - Delivery Reports and Complaints, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 9)
    - Dinah, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 10)
    - Dinners: Staff: Giambelli: January 26, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 11)
    - Dinners: Windows On The World Dinner: June 29, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 12)
    - Direct Mail, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 13)
    - Distribution: Misses, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 14)
    - Donath, Bob Column: Daily News, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 15)
    - Donohue Show, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 16)
    - Edit: Close and Misses, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 17)
    - Edit: Production: Five Plants, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 18)
    - Esquire, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 19)
    - Estimates, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 20)
    - Evaluations, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 21)
    - Faces Magazine, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 22)
    - Family Circle, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 23)
    - Federal Trade Commission, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 24)
    - Filler Space, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 25)
    - Five-Year Plan, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 26)
    - Focus Magazine (Australia), 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 27)
    - Free Space Requests, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 28)
    - Free Sub Requests, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 29)
    - Golf, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 30)
    - Golf: DAA, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 31)
    - Golf: "Legends of Golf": Austin, Texas: April 26-28, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 32)
    - Golf: Detroit Golf Invitational: May 22, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 33)
    - Golf: Anama VIP Pro-Am Golf: June 19, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 34)
    - Golf: Chicago Gold Outing: Shoreacres: June 27-28, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 35)
    - Golf: National Golf Links: July 12-13, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 36)
    - Golf: Time Inc. Invitational: July 24-25, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 37)
    - Golf: Arcata National Corporation: Aspertuck Country Club: September 7, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 38)
    - Golf: National Golf Links: September 20-21, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 39)
    - Golf: National Golf Links: Supermarket People: September 28, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 40)
    - Golf: Time Inc. Golf: LaQuinta: December 14-15, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 41)
    - Hall Magazine Editorial Reports, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 42)
    - Home Box Office (HBO), 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 43)
    - Ideas: Ad Expo, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 44)
    - Ideas for People, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 45)
    - Inserts, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 46)
    - International, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 47)
    - International: Australia, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 48)
    - International: England, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 49)
    - International: European Representation, 1978 (Offsite-box 2955, Folder 50)
    - Intercorporate Group, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 1)
    - Kotter, John: Harvard University Session: December 12-14, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 2)
    - Legal, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 3-4)
    - Legal: Logo, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 5)
    - Legal: Logo: Modern People, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 6)
    - Letters, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 7)
    - Letters: Circulation Complaints, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 8)
    - Letters; Complaints on Stories, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 9)
    - Letters: Miscellaneous, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 10)
    - Letters: Per Person Versus Billing, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 11)
    - Letters: Pricing, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 12)
    - Letters: Requests for Story Coverage, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 13)
    - Letters: Too Much Advertising, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 14)
    - Life, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 15)
    - Liquor Category, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 16)
    - Look, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 17)
    - Luncheons/Dinners: Agencies, Advertisers, Etc., 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 18)
    - Madison Avenue, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 19)
    - Magazines, Newspapers, Tabloids, Etc., 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 20)
    - Mailings: 1978 Diary (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 21)
    - Mailings: Andre Watts Album, 1978 (Offsite-box 2956, Folder 22)